Guide to the Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera, 1840-2016 and undated RL.00580
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Kenneth Hubbard collection of presidential campaign ephemera
1840-2016 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.00580
30 Linear Feet
Kenneth Hubbard is an avid collector of campaign memorabilia. The Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera consists of printed and artifactural memorabilia from assorted presidential campaigns, dating largely from the late nineteenth century through the present. Items are chiefly relating to the Democratic and Republican political parties, with some materials from the U.S. Socialist Party and the Prohibitionist Party. The majority of the collection consists of buttons, pins, and campaign literature such as pamphlets, newsletters, flyers, and platforms. Arranged by year and candidate name.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2006, 2008, 2012, 2015, and 2016.
Collection Overview
The Kenneth Hubbard Collection of Presidential Campaign Ephemera consists of printed and artifactual memorabilia from assorted presidential campaigns, dating largely from the late nineteenth century through the present. Items are chiefly relating to the Democratic and Republican political parties, with some materials from the U.S. Socialist Party and the Prohibitionist Party. The majority of the collection consists of buttons, pins, and campaign literature such as pamphlets, newsletters, flyers, and platforms. There are also speech transcripts from appearances by John F. Kennedy and Adlai Stevenson during their presidential campaigns.
Related Materials
The David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library holds thousands of bound pamphlets and manuscript collections relating to United States elections, as well as archival collections focused on individual political figures, particularly in the state of North Carolina, and Durham, Orange, and Wake counties.
Arrangement
Materials are presented here by election year and candidate. Some candidates who ran for office several times have undated buttons or pins that cannot be dated to a precise election year. These items are listed in the last series, and arranged by candidate name and decade.
Political participation; Political parties -- United States -- History; Political campaigns -- United States -- History; Elections -- United States -- History; Buttons (information artifacts); Memorabilia; Presidential candidates -- United States; Presidents -- United States -- Inauguration; Presidents -- United States -- Election; Democratic Party (U.S.) -- History; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Socialist Party (U.S.) -- History
- 1828 Campaign, 1829
  - Jackson, Andrew, 1829
    - Gold victory button, eagle with shield on front. Text on back: Jackson Victory, 1829 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-AXJ1829-001)
- 1840 Campaign
  - Harrison, William Henry, 1840
    - Pin with log cabin and text: Harrison & Reform, 1840 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WHH1840-001)
    - Brass shell badge with trefoil-shaped corners and log cabin house image with text: Harrison & Reform, 1840 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-WHH1840-002)
- 1856 Campaign
  - Buchanan, James, 1856
    - A medalet adorned with stars, a buck, and a cannon with an image of George Washington on the other side and text: "The Union Must & Shall Be Preserved" and "United We Stand Divided We Fall.", 1856 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-JXB1856-001)
    - Framed Portrait of James Buchanan's vice president J.C. Breckinridge, 1856 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-JXB1856-002)
- 1860 Campaign
  - Douglas, Stephen Arnold, 1860
    - Pin brass frame with ferrotype portraits of Douglas and Johnson with text: Stephen A. Douglas, Heschel V. Johnson, 1860 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SAD1860-001)
    - Pin brass frame with ferrotype portraits of Douglas and Johnson with text: Stephen A. Douglas, Heschel V. Johnson, 1860 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SAD1860-002)
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1860
    - Pin with brass frame and ferrotype portraits of Lincoln and Hamblin with text: Union of the States 1860, The Constitution and Laws 1860 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-AXL1860-001)
- 1864 Campaign
  - Lincoln, Abraham, 1864
    - Badge with ferrotype of Lincoln and text: A. Lincoln, 1864 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-AXL1864-001)
      Scope and Contents
      From Benjamin T. Towner Papers.
    - Framed Portrait of Abraham Lincoln, 1864 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-AXL1864-002)
  - McClellan, George Brinton, 1864
    - Shield brass with ferrotype of McClellan, 1864 (Box 31, Item RL-005801864-GBM-001)
- 1868 Campaign
  - Grant, Ulysses S., 1868
    - Pin rectangle with portraits of Grant and Colfax, 1868 (Box 31, Item RL-005801868-USG-001)
    - Pin rectangle with portrait of Grant in brass frame, 1868 (Box 31, Item RL-005801868-USG-002)
    - Pin, six-point-star in brass openwork with ferrotype portrait of Grant and text: U. S. Grant, 1868 (Box 31, Item RL-005801868-USG-003)
    - Hanging badge with back-to-back portraits of Grant and Colfax suspended from eagle-form pinback hanger bar, 1868 (Box 31, Item RL-005801868-USG-004)
  - Seymour, Horatio, 1868
    - Pin with cameo of Seymour and text: This is a White Man's Government, 1868 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-HXS1868-001)
    - Eagle pin with star and portrait of Horatio Seymour, 1868 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-HXS1868-002)
- 1872 Campaign
  - Greeley, Horace, 1872
    - Pin with silk-covered frame with ferrotype of Greeley with text: Greeley, 1872 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-HXG1872-001)
- 1876 Campaign
  - Hayes, Rutherford Birchard, 1876
    - Badge with ferrotype of Hayes and text: Our Centennial President, 1876 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-RBH1876-001)
  - Tilden, Samuel Jones, 1876
    - Pin, brass surrounded by blue band with portraits of Tilden and Hendricks, 1876 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SJT1876-001)
- 1880 Campaign
  - Garfield, James Abram, 1880
    - Coin with James A. Garfield portrait, 1880 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-JAG1880-001)
    - Pin with James A. Garfield portrait, 1880 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-JAG1880-002)
    - Button with text: Garfield and Arthur, 188- (Box 31, Item RL-00580-JAG1880-003)
    - "Garfield and Arthur Republican Campaign Song Book," Republican Central Campaign Club, 1880 (Box 13)
  - Hancock, Winfield Scott, 1880
    - Pin with daguerrotype of Hancock and text: Our Presidential Candidates, 1880 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WSH1880-001)
    - Gilded Button with portrait of Winfield Scott, 1880 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WSH1880-002)
- 1884 Campaign
  - Blaine, James Gillespie, 1884
    - Pin with gilded broche and pendant with portrait of James G Blaine and VP candidate, 1884 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-JGB1884-001)
    - Pin with image of Blaine and VP Candidate, 1884 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-JGB1884-002)
  - Cleveland, Grover, 1884
    - Coin with profile image of Cleveland and Hendricks, with text: Cleveland & Hendricks on a broad platform of good planks will lead all to victory, 1884 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SGC1884-001)
    - Badge brass shell frame with ferrotype of Cleveland, 1884 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SGC1884-002)
- 1888 Campaign
  - Cleveland, Grover, 1888
    - Kerchief, 1888 (Oversize-folder 1, Item RL-00580-SGC1888-001)
    - Coin, with profile images of Cleveland and Thurman with text: Reform, A Public Office is a Public Trust, 1888 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SGC1888-002)
    - Match safe, spring-loaded catch in image of Cleveland, 1888 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SGC1888-003)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1888
    - Button with woven cloth flag and text: Harrison, 1888 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-BXH1888-001)
    - Coin with profile images of Harrison and Morton with text: Protection to home industries, 1888 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-BXH1888-002)
- 1892 Campaign
  - Cleveland, Grover, 1892
    - Pin brown, with text: Cleveland Stevenson, 1892 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-SGC1892-001)
  - Harrison, Benjamin, 1892
    - Pin with portrait of Benjamin Harrison, 1892 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-BXH1892-001)
- 1896 Campaign
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1896
    - Postcard: Pull for your candidate, 1896 (Box 13)
    - Button portrait of Bryan, words: Free Silver 1896, W.J. Bryan printed under picture (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-001)
    - Button portrait of Bryan, words: Victory 1896, W.J. Bryan printed under picture (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-002)
    - Button with 16-1 printed, blue background, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-003)
    - Pin with silver beetle, words: No Compromise 16 to 1, blue background, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-004)
    - Silver clock button, 16 to 1, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-005)
    - Silver button, words: Free Coinage, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-006)
    - Pin with flower, 1 in center, petals counting from 1 to 16, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-007)
    - Silver button, dollar sign, 1896 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1896-008)
  - McKinley, William, 1896
    - Button with text Republican Phalanx and printed photographs of McKinley & Hobart, 1896 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-001)
    - Button with text: Protection '96 and original photograph of McKinley, 1896 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-002)
    - Gold Policy Button with text: Nothing like Gold, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-003)
    - Gold Policy Button shaped like a bird with a hat on with text: Gold, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-004)
    - Gold Policy Beatle, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-005)
    - Large Gold Policy Beatle, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-006)
    - Golden Policy Beatle, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-007)
    - Ribbon pin with photograph of McKinley with text: Protection Prosperity, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-008)
    - Gold Policy button Flying Beatle, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-009)
      Conditions Governing Access
      broken
    - Portraits of McKinley and Hobart, with words Sound Money Protection. American flag background., 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-010)
    - Portraits of McKinley and Hobart, names printed overhead, 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-011)
    - Brass button with eagle on it. McKinley and Hobart printed on button., 1896 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-012)
    - Mechanical gold bug with photograph portraits of McKinley and Hobart, 1896 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-WXM1896-013)
- 1900 Campaign
  - McKinley, William, 1900
    - Button with printed photographs of McKinley and Roosevelt, 1900 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-001)
    - Pin with American banner and image of McKinley and Roosevelt with text: Commercial Travelers Republican Club, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-002)
    - Pin with American banner and image of McKinley with text: Brooklyn Young Republican Club 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-003)
    - Wooden Button with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt with American flag ribbon image, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-004)
    - McKinley Roosevelt photograph button with banner with text: Executive Com., 1900 (Box Unknown-Box-2, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-005)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, American flag strip in background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-006)
    - Pin with two portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, red white and blue ribbon background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-007)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt with names printed above heads, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-008)
    - Pin with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, American flag on shield background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-009)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, American flag under portrait in background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-010)
    - Pin small with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, red white blue ribbon background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-011)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, some American flag in background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-012)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, American flag in background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-013)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, names printed under, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-014)
    - Pin gold portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-015)
    - Pin with portrait of Mckinley and Roosevelt, American flag over portrait, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-016)
    - Pin with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, American flag on shield background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-017)
    - Pin with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, ribbon background over portrait, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-018)
    - Pin small with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, red white blue ribbon background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-019)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, strip American flag background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-020)
    - Pin with portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, blue and gold background, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-021)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-022)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt on tin box, with words sound money-good markets. Cup with words Employment for Labor on top. blue background., 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-023)
    - Button with McKinley and Roosevelt portrait, flag around button, white ribbon, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-024)
    - Pin small with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt on tin box, with words sound money-good markets. Cup with words Employment for Labor on top. blue background., 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-025)
    - Gold pin piece, two portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt on each side, writing of Get In To The GOP in middle, 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-026)
    - Pin with portrait of McKinley and Roosevelt, faded., 1900 (Box 21, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-027)
    - Pin with colorized portraits of McKinley and Roosevelt, 1900 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-WXM1900-028)
- 1904 Campaign
  - Parker, Alton Brooks, 1904
    - Pin color portrait of Parker and Davis, names printed under, 1904 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-ABP1904-001)
    - Pin black and white portraits of Parker and Davis, names printed under. Eagle in background, American flag under portraits., 1904 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-ABP1904-002)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1904
    - large metal pendant with engraved imagers of Roosevelt and Fairbanks and text: Trade follows the flag, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-001)
    - button with image of playing cards and portrait of Roosevelt and text: Stand Pat, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-002)
    - 1904 Theodore Roosevelt Jugate Button (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-003)
    - 1904 Theodore Roosevelt Jugate Button (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-004)
    - 1904 Theodore Roosevelt Jugate Button with Bald Eagle illustration (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-005)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Rough Rider button, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-006)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt with Fairbanks, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-007)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt with Fairbanks, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-008)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt with Fairbanks, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-009)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt with Fairbanks, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-010)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt Button, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-011)
    - 1904 Theodore Roosevelt Jugate Button (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-012)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt surrounded by American flag button, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-013)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt surrounded by American flag and gold border button, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-014)
    - Portrait of Roosevelt with text: Theodore Roosevelt, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-015)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Rough Rider button surrounded by American flag, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-016)
    - White Ribbon with plague with text: Roosevelt and Fairbanks 1904 Washington (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-017)
    - Red button with text: T.R., 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-018)
    - Portrait of Roosevelt with text: Theodore Roosevelt, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-019)
    - blue button with text: T.R., 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-020)
    - Sepia portrait of Roosevelt, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-021)
    - Rough Rider pin, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-022)
    - Roosevelt Pin, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-023)
    - Roosevelt and Fairbanks 1904 election medal (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-024)
    - Medal with ribbon and printed photograph of Roosevelt in shield, with text: Republican Captain 1904 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-025)
    - Pin with American flag and printed photographs of Roosevelt and Fairbanks with ribbon attached, 1904 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-026)
    - Medal with blue ribbon and gold metal imprint of capitol building, with text: Washington, 1905, Inauguration President Roosevelt (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-027)
    - Medal with printed colorized photograph of Roosevelt with blue ribbon attached, with text: President, Inauguration, March 4th 1905 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-028)
    - Pin in shape of belt buckle with leather strap with text: Roosevelt Fairbanks 1904 Washington (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-029)
    - Belt with buckle and text: For President Theodore Roosevelt, 1904 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1904-030)
- 1908 Campaign
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1908
    - Leather belt with metal buckle. words: Bryan and Kern 1908 Washington. (Box 22, Item RL-00580-WJB1908-001)
    - Yellow Ribbon portrait of Bryan. Words: Welcome to the People's Friend William J. Bryan. Oct. 12, 1909 Seattle (Box Unknown-Box-3, Item RL-00580-WJB1909-001)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1908
    - Leather belt with metal shield, words: Taft and Sherman 1908 Washington (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-001)
    - Pin portraits of Taft and Sherman, green background with red and white stripes, 1908 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-002)
    - Pin portraits of Taft and Sherman, sepia, 1908 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-003)
    - Metal badge portrait of Taft and Sherman, 1908 over. Words: Our Choice Taft & Sherman (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-004)
    - Ash tray or saucer. Portraits of Taft and Sherman, white house in background. Words: Grand Old Party 1856 to 1908, names of past Presidents on left and right of portraits. (Box Unknown-Box-1, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-005)
    - Pin portrait of Taft and Sherman, sepia, 1908 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1908-006)
    - Pin souvenir, words: Inauguration Washington D.C. March 4th 1909, on red and white ribbon. Cross medal at bottom with portrait of Taft. (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1909-001)
- 1912 Campaign
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1912
    - Progressive Bull moose button, 1912 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-001)
    - Portrait of Theodore Roosevelt black and white on button, 1912 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-002)
    - Sepia portrait of Theodore Roosevelt on button, 1912 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-003)
    - Presidential Coin with image of Roosevelt, 1912 (Box 22, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-004)
    - Bull moose pin, 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-005)
    - Bull moose pin, 1912 (Box 31, Item RL-00580-TXR1912-006)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1912
    - Button with printed photograph of Taft, 1912 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WHT1912-001)
    - Button with printed photographs of Taft and Sherman, 1912 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-WHT1912-002)
    - Gold pin, words: Taft & Sherman 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-WHT1912-003)
  - Wilson, Thomas Woodrow, 1912
    - Woodrow Wilson Clock with portrait of Woodrow Wilson, 1912 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-TWW1912-001)
    - Pin with printed photograph of Wilson with text: Woodrow Wilson for president 1912 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW1912-002)
- 1916 Campaign
  - Benson, Allan, 1916
    - Socialist Party campaign literature, 1916 (Box 13)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1916
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Hughes, 1916 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-CEH1916-001)
    - Pin, shield with red white and blue stripes, words: Hughes, on blue. White background., 1916 (Box 23, Item RL-00580-CEH1916-002)
  - Johnson, Hiram Warren, 1916
    - Pin with red, white, and blue stripes and printed photograph of Johnson, with text: America First, Johnson for President, 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-HWJ1916-001)
  - Wilson, Thomas Woodrow, 1916
    - Pin with red, white, and blue stripes and portraits of Wilson and Marshall and text: They have kept the faith, America First, We'll Stand By Them, 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW1916-001)
    - Pin yellow, with text: War in Europe, Peace in America, God Bless Wilson, 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW1916-002)
    - Pin white, with printed photograph of Wilson, with text: He proved the pen mightier than the sword, 1916 (Box 33, Item RL-00580-TWW1916-003)
- 1920 Campaign
  - Debs, Eugene Victor, 1920
    - Button with printed photographs of Debs and Seymour Stedman and text: Debs and Stedman, 1920 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-EVD1920-001)
    - Socialist Party Platform, 1920 (Box 13)
  - Cox, James Middleton, 1920
    - Blue pin with rooster. Words: Don't Croak, Crow!, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JMC1920-001)
  - Harding, Warren Gamaliel, 1920
    - Pin portrait of Harding, sepia, blue surrounding. Words: For President Warren G. Harding, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-001)
    - Blue pin, words: Harding and Coolidge. Two stars., 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-002)
    - Small pin portrait of Harding, sepia, blue surrounding. Words: For President Warren G. Harding, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-003)
    - Pin portrait of Harding, sepia, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-004)
    - Red pin with blue horizontal stripe. Words: Harding and Coolidge, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-005)
    - Blue pin, words: Harding and Coolidge, 1920 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-WGH1920-006)
- 1924 Campaign
  - Coolidge, John Calvin, 1924
    - Button with printed photograph of Coolidge and text: National Coolidge College Clubs, 1924 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-001)
    - Button with printed photographs of Coolidge and Dawes and text: Vote for The Republican Candidates for President and Vice President 1924 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-002)
    - Blue pin, elephant with words: Coolidge and Dawes, 1924 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-003)
    - Pin red and blue, words: Coolidge-Dawes Full Dinner Pail. Picture of dinner pail., 1924 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-004)
    - Pin portraits of Coolidge, Fuller and Gillett, black and white. Names printed under, 1924 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-005)
    - Pin red white and blue, words: Coolidge and Dawes, 1924 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-006)
    - Finger thimble, words: Coolidge and Dawes on blue stripe., 1924 (Box 27, Item RL-00580-JCC1924-007)
  - Davis, John William, 1924
    - Pin brown, with text: Davis and Brown, 1924 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-JWD1924-001)
  - LaFollette, Robert Marion, 1924
    - Campaign literature and publications by the Progressive Party, 1924 (Box 13)
    - Pin with blue border and liberty bell in center, with text: La Follette Wheeler '76, 1924 (Box 32, Item RL-00580-RML1924-001)
- 1928 Campaign
  - Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1928
    - Button with printed photographs of Smith and Robinson and text: Smith and Robinson, 1928 (Box 1, Item RL-00580-ALS1928-001)